<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business Software Solutions on ERP Tech</title>
    <link>https://erptech.pl/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business Software Solutions on ERP Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://erptech.pl/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy &amp; Cookies</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy ERP Tech (hereinafter: &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;) respects your privacy. This policy explains how we collect, use, and protect your personal data.&#xA;1. Data Controller The controller of your personal data is:&#xA;ERP Tech Sp. z o.o. Address: [Your address] Email: [Your email] Phone: [Your phone] 2. What data do we collect? We collect data in the following situations:&#xA;Contact form: name, email, subject, message Analytics: anonymous traffic data (anonymized IP, browser type, visited pages, time spent) Cookies: session identifiers, user preferences 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrations</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/services/integrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/services/integrations/</guid>
      <description>Integrations for SAP &amp;amp; ERPNext We design integrations that keep your data consistent across systems and reduce manual work:&#xA;API integrations (REST, SOAP) EDI and file-based exchange Middleware and event-driven flows Reporting and data synchronization Monitoring and error handling If you need a specific integration scenario, contact us and we’ll propose the safest and fastest approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lean ERP</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/services/lean-erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/services/lean-erp/</guid>
      <description>Lean ERP – Waste Elimination Methodology&#xD;At ERPtech, we implement ERP systems based on Lean Manufacturing principles. We eliminate waste, optimize flows, and build continuous improvement cultures – all within one integrated system.&#xA;Waste elimination. We identify and remove 8 types of Muda (overproduction, waiting, transport, overprocessing, inventory, unnecessary movement, defects, unused potential).&#xA;Continuous improvement (Kaizen). Built-in KPI monitoring mechanisms, bottleneck analysis, and optimization suggestions.&#xA;Value stream mapping. Mapping processes from raw material to finished product with clear visualization of value added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Who We Are? ERP Tech is a team of experienced specialists with years of experience in implementing and expanding ERPnext and SAP systems. We are the main representative of ERPnext in Poland.&#xA;Our Mission Our mission is to support companies in digital transformation by providing the best ERP solutions tailored to each client&amp;rsquo;s individual needs.&#xA;10+&#xD;Years of experience&#xA;100+&#xD;Completed projects&#xA;50+&#xD;Satisfied clients&#xA;Why Choose Us? Experience - Years of experience in ERP implementations Professionalism - Highest quality of services Support - Comprehensive support at every stage of the project Innovation - We use the latest technologies Want to learn more?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>&#xD;Name *&#xD;Email *&#xD;Subject&#xD;Message&#xD;Send Message&#xD;biuro@erptech.pl&#xD;(+48) 693 068 300&#xD;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EOD</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/services/eod/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/services/eod/</guid>
      <description>EOD System in ERPnext ERPnext offers a comprehensive electronic document management solution:&#xA;Document creation and management Workflows and business processes Version control Electronic signatures Integration with other modules Document Templates&#xD;Ready-made templates for invoices, contracts, orders and other documents.&#xD;Workflows&#xD;Defining business processes and approval paths.&#xD;Versioning&#xD;Full history of document changes.&#xD;E-Signatures&#xD;Option to add qualified electronic signatures.&#xD;Benefits Security - document access control Efficiency - elimination of paper documents Tracking - full history of changes and approvals Integration - automatic document generation from other modules Interested in implementation?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERPnext System</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/services/erpnext/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/services/erpnext/</guid>
      <description>Main ERPnext Representative in Poland ERPnext is an open source ERP system offering full functionality without license costs. We are the main ERPnext representative in Poland with years of experience in implementing and customizing this system.&#xA;No License&#xD;Open source without license costs&#xA;Modularity&#xD;Choose only needed modules&#xA;Mobility&#xD;Access from any device&#xA;Customization&#xD;Tailored to your needs&#xA;ERPnext Modules Warehouse&#xD;Comprehensive warehouse and logistics management.&#xD;Learn more →&#xD;Production&#xD;Production planning, BOM, work orders and quality control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job Offers</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/careers/</guid>
      <description>Current Job Openings&#xD;Python Intern - Frappe/ERPNext&#xD;Internship&#xD;Remote/Hybrid&#xD;Python&#xD;Posted: November 7, 2025&#xA;About the Position&#xD;We are looking for an ambitious intern who wants to develop Python skills and learn the Frappe framework and ERPNext system. This is a great opportunity to gain practical experience with modern open-source ERP.&#xD;Requirements&#xD;Basic knowledge of Python&#xD;Willingness to learn and grow in ERP systems&#xD;Basic HTML, CSS, JavaScript knowledge is a plus&#xD;Teamwork skills&#xD;Good communication skills&#xD;English sufficient to read technical documentation&#xD;We Offer&#xD;Practical experience with ERPNext and Frappe&#xD;Mentoring from experienced developers&#xD;Remote or hybrid work&#xD;Flexible working hours&#xD;Friendly work environment&#xD;Possibility of employment after internship&#xD;Participation in real client projects&#xD;Responsibilities&#xD;Support in ERPNext development and customization&#xD;Creating and modifying DocTypes in Frappe&#xD;Writing automation scripts&#xD;Creating reports and dashboards&#xD;Testing and debugging&#xD;Code and solution documentation&#xD;Technologies&#xD;Python&#xD;Frappe Framework&#xD;ERPNext&#xD;JavaScript&#xD;MariaDB&#xD;Git&#xD;Linux&#xD;Apply Now&#xD;Send your CV and cover letter to:&#xD;biuro@erptech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Production</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/services/production/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/services/production/</guid>
      <description>ERPnext Production Module ERPnext enables comprehensive production management:&#xA;BOM (Bill of Materials) definition Work order creation Production capacity planning Production progress tracking Cost calculation Warehouse integration Product Cards&#xD;Full specification of products and components.&#xD;Product Structures&#xD;Multi-level BOM definitions with alternative versions.&#xD;Work Orders&#xD;Planning and execution of production orders.&#xD;Production Reports&#xD;Analysis of production efficiency and costs.&#xD;Benefits Optimization - better resource utilization Control - real-time progress tracking Flexibility - adaptation to different production models Integration - connection with warehouse and finance Interested in implementation?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP FIORI</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/services/fiori/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/services/fiori/</guid>
      <description>SAP FIORI - interface revolution SAP FIORI is a modern, responsive user interface for SAP systems:&#xA;UX-driven design Access from any device View personalization Intuitive navigation Ready-to-use apps for various business processes Responsiveness&#xD;Full functionality on computers, tablets and smartphones.&#xD;Personalization&#xD;Interface customization to user needs.&#xD;Performance&#xD;Fast loading and smooth operation.&#xD;Security&#xD;Advanced authentication and authorization mechanisms.&#xD;Our Services SAP FIORI Implementation - full installation and configuration Migration from SAP GUI - smooth transition to new interface App Development - custom FIORI apps creation Integrations - connection with other systems Training - user preparation Interested in implementation?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP IoT</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/services/iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/services/iot/</guid>
      <description>SAP IoT - smart solutions We integrate IoT devices with SAP systems:&#xA;Sensor data collection Real-time data analysis Process automation Predictive maintenance ERP and MES integration IoT Devices&#xD;Integration of various sensors and devices.&#xD;SAP Cloud&#xD;Secure data storage and analysis.&#xD;Data Analysis&#xD;Advanced data analysis algorithms.&#xD;Automation&#xD;Automatic reactions to events.&#xD;Benefits Savings - cost reduction through monitoring Efficiency - production process optimization Prediction - failure forecasting Reports - comprehensive data summaries Interested in solution?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warehouse</title>
      <link>https://erptech.pl/en/services/warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erptech.pl/en/services/warehouse/</guid>
      <description>ERPnext Warehouse System ERPnext offers full warehouse management functionality including:&#xA;Stock level tracking Location management Goods receipt and issue Inventory counts Batch and serial number management Integration with purchases and sales Barcodes&#xD;Generate and scan barcodes for quick item identification.&#xD;Stock Transfers&#xD;Manage item transfers between warehouses.&#xD;Inventory&#xD;Plan and conduct inventory counts with variance reports.&#xD;Logistics&#xD;Manage deliveries and transportation.&#xD;Benefits Automation - minimize human errors Integration - full connection with sales and purchase modules Reports - analysis of warehouse turnover Mobility - access from mobile devices Interested in implementation?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
